jimmy.com 2019-02-02

# Privacy Policy

_Privacy Policy_

Last updated: August 21, 2017                     

Welcome to [www.jimmy.com](http://www.jimmy.com/) (“Website” or “Site”) owned and operated by Whirlwind Enterprises Limited (hereinafter referred to as **“Company”,   “We”, “Us” or “Our”**) operating in accordance with the laws of England and Wales with its registered office located at 1B Stile Hall Parade London W4 3AG United Kingdom. We act as your data controller. If you have any questions about this privacy policy such as: what information we collect from you and how we use that information or if you simply want to know what information we have about you on our records, please contact us at [help@jimmy.com](mailto:help@jimmy.com) and we will respond to your query within five working days. 

We are respectful of the privacy of our Users. Please read this Policy carefully to inform yourself about our business practices with regards to the collection and use of your personal data. If you do not expressly agree with our policy as described hereunder please refrain from using our Website and Services. By registering an account on [www.jimmy.com](http://www.jimmy.com/) or purchasing a product through our site, you give us your full consent to the collection and use of your Personal Information as stated herein.

**Modification**

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion without giving any prior notice to you. In the event we decide to make any changes to our practices and policies, we will inform you of such amendments by changing the last updated date on the top of this page. Please take a few minutes of your time to review this Policy periodically. A change will be effective when posted on this web page and the notice will be given by amendment to the last updated date on the top.

**Collection of personal information** ****

There is certain information that you expressly provide us when you register an account on our website or order a product through our site. This information includes your full name, email address, phone number and delivery address (“Personally identifiable information”). 

Information we collect about your from your use of our Website

There is certain information that we are able to collect about you through the use of log data and other internal analytics tools we use to gain intelligence on the performance of your services such as your IP address, the pages you visit on our site, date and time of your visits (“Non-Personally Identifiable Information”).

**How we use the information we collect**

We use your personally identifiable information to contact you, ship the ordered product to you, send you newsletter when you subscribe to receive newsletter from us and to improve our services to you. Please note that we may occasionally use your personally identifiable information to send marketing material to you. 

We do not and never will sell or rent your personal and business information to any person or entity with the exception of the event where we undergo a merger or acquisition. 

**Sharing your information**

Please note that we may be required to disclose your personal information to local or international law enforcement authorities or governmental bodies upon reasonable requests or to third-party service providers in the event of security breach of system, networks or website. We may also share your information with our partners and any service provider that we may engage to help us in facilitating our Services to you and to assist us with intelligent analysis of how our users interact with our Website. 

In the event where any Service Providers we engage comes in contact with your personally identifiable information, please be assured that we have entered into confidentiality agreements with such Service Provider and their access to your information is only in the course of performing these tasks on our behalf. 

**Marketing Communications**

From time to time we may use your personally identifiable information to send you content  that we think you will find interesting. You can easily opt out of receiving communication from us, at any time, by simply clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our email or by simply contacting us at [help@jimmy.com](mailto:help@jimmy.com).

**Processing your data**

We process all personally identifiable information and business information on computers and servers that are located in UK and in accordance with data protection laws applicable in UK. By creating an account on our Website or purchasing products on our site, you consent to such processing of your personally identifiable information. ****

**Security of your data**

We strive to keep all your personally identifiable information secure. We use all commercially viable means and industry best practices to protect your Personal Information but you understand that our website is built upon third-party software and hardware which may possess vulnerabilities and therefore we are unable to offer any guarantees for security of your personal information.

**Retention of data**

We assure you that we will not retain any of your personally identifiable information for a period longer than necessary for fulfilment of our business and legal requirements. We reserve the right to retain your personal information for a period of five years after your account is terminated but we do not have any obligation towards you to retain such information and we may in our sole discretion discard your personal information from our records sooner. 

**Use of Cookies**

Like most other website nowadays, we make use of cookies to enhance our User experience. Cookies are small files with data that helps Us to uniquely identify You as a User without linking any personally identifiable information with these unique identifier files. You have the choice to either instruct Your browser to decline all cookies or to indicate to You when a cookie is being sent. In the event that You choose to decline cookies from Our Website, You understand that You may not be able to use some parts of Our Website and Services We offer.

                                    ****

**Disclaimer for third-party website links**

Our Website may contain links to third party websites that are neither owned nor operated by us. Should you decide to click on any such third party links, you will be directed to such third party website. These third-party sites have their own Terms of Service and Privacy Policy and we encourage you to review their Terms and Privacy Policy prior to using their site or any services offered by them.

We disclaim all liability with regards to your use and access of such third-party sites. We cannot be held responsible for any content made available by these third-party sites or their practices. You access and use these sites solely at your own risk.

**Protection of Children’s Privacy**

Our website is not aimed at people who are under the age of eighteen (18) years ("Children") without the express consent of their parent(s)/legal guardian(s). If you are the parent / legal guardian of a Child who you believe has provided us with his/her personally identifiable information without your express consent, please contact us immediately and we will take steps to remove such personally identifiable information from our database and servers immediately.

**Right to Access Your Personally Identifiable Information**

You have the right to request to access your personally identifiable information that we hold and to update or edit this information to ensure it is current and accurate. To exercise your right you can contact us at [help@jimmy.com](mailto:help@jimmy.com).
